

Contact information

0

Address

La Plata, Buenos Aires, Argentina (ZIP 1900)



Phone

+54 9 011 23864313



Mail

Jfschallibaum@gmail.com



Github:

/JohnFScha



LinkedIn:

in/juan-francisco-schallibaum



Portfolio:

https://www.johnfscha.site

Skills



React



Node



MongoDB



JavaScript



HTML5



CSS3

Languages

Spanish

Native

English

Profficient (C2)

JUAN FRANCISCO SCHALLIBAUM

Full Stack Developer.

Open for remote work / Relocation proposals.



About me

Passionate Fullstack Developer with experience in JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, React.js, Node.js and Next.js, complemented by a background in psychology. Excited to contribute to collaborative teams and continue growing in this field. My psychology degree provides me with a unique ability to establish effective client relationships, allowing me to deeply understand their needs and create customized solutions. I am dedicated to creating user - centered applications that not only meet technical requirements but also offer engaging and enjoyable user experiences.



Work Experience

Freelance Frontend Developer

September 2022 to today (1 year, 2 months)

- · Wireframing.
- Development of personal web pages.
- Development of landing pages.
- Development of e-commerce websites.

Clinical Psychologyst | General Hospital "Dr. Prof. Rodolfo Rossi"

June2019 to August 2023 (4 years, 2 months)

- Conducted individual and group therapy.
- Performed epidemiological research.
- Given lectures and classes.
- Written in-depth clinical reports.

Education



Sep. 2022 - May 2023

@Coderhouse

Frontend Development Career

March 2011 - Oct. 2018

National University of La Plata

BSc in Pyschology

Online Courses

Sep. 2023

Sep. 2023

Jan 2024

Sep. 2022 - Dec 2022 <u>@Coderhouse</u>: *Web development* □

Dec 2022 - Feb. 2023 <u>@Coderhouse</u>: *JavaScript* [∠]

Feb. 2023 - May 2023 <u>@Coderhouse: React.js</u> [2]

May 2023 - Aug. 2023 <u>@Leniolabs</u>: Frontend Bootcamp

<u>@CertiProf: Remote Working Professional</u> [2]

@CertiProf: SCRUM Working Professional [2]

@Coderhouse: Next.JS [2]